https://oltraining.com/ec/terms-conditions

Terms & Conditions
Terms & Conditions
OnLine Training, Inc. considers itself an Educational Institute. As such we have modeled our policies from those of several colleges and universities, with the requisite modifications needed for an online institution. The terms and and conditions listed on this page are here to protect ourselves and our students. For further information please contact OLT.
Click on a topic to read more about it.
PRIVACY POLICY
TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE
TRADEMARKS, COPYRIGHTS AND RESTRICTIONS
REFUND POLICY
LINKED SITES
BULLETIN BOARDS/CHAT ROOMS and Non-Moderated List Servers
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY/ DISCLAIMER
JURISDICTIONAL ISSUES
OTHER
_________________________________________
PRIVACY POLICY
Thank you for visiting OnLine Training Institute's Web site. Your privacy is very important to us. We collect no personal information about you when you visit our Web site unless you choose to make such information available to us.
When you visit our Web site, our server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.
In addition, we monitor the volume and timing of access to our site by collecting information on the date, time and pages accessed by visitors. We do this so that we can improve the content of our Web site, and this information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and individual visitors' personal information is not identified.
If you choose to share personal information with us - by sending us a message or filling out an electronic form with personal information - we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized. Some of the Information may be saved for a designated period to comply with Florida's archiving policies, but we will not disclose the information to third parties or other government agencies, unless required to do so by state or federal law.
Students our server maintains a record of all usernames logged into one of our courses. This monitoring is designed to assist us in improving our courses. We may report your onsite activity to an individual or school for their records. We may use this information in internal research and in the writing of academic papers. OLT will not in any way release your personal information to third parties or government agencies.
If you have any other questions about our privacy procedures, or have ideas about improving our procedures, please feel free to e-mail us at register@oltraining.com.
Back to Top
_________________________________________
TERMS AND CONDITIONS
This site (the "Site") is owned and operated by OnLine Training, Inc. ("OLT") for your personal information, education and communication. Please feel free to browse the Site; however, your access and use of the Site is subject to the following terms and conditions ("Terms and Conditions") and all applicable laws. By accessing and browsing the Site, you accept, without limitation or qualification, the Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree with any of the below Terms and Conditions, do not use the Site. OnLine Training reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update these Terms and Conditions at any time and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.
Back to Top
_________________________________________
TRADEMARKS, COPYRIGHTS AND RESTRICTIONS
All material on this site, including, but not limited to images, illustrations, audio clips, and video clips, is protected by copyrights which are owned and controlled by OnLine Training or by other parties that have licensed their material to ("Material"). Material from the Site or any web site owned, operated, licensed or controlled by Online Training may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way with out the expressed written permision of Online Training, Inc. Modification of the Materials or use of the Materials for any other purpose is a violation of the copyrights and other proprietary rights. For purposes of these Terms and Conditions, the use of any such material on any other web site or networked computer environment is prohibited.
The trademarks, logos and service marks ("Marks") displayed on the Site are the property of Online Training and other parties. Users are prohibited from using any Marks without the written permission of Online Training or such third party which may own the Marks.
Back to Top
_________________________________________
REFUND POLICY
Online Training, Inc. actively seeks to create learning environments that fully foster the success of those that use our instructional materials. Barriers to learning are by design eliminated from our course offerings. One known barrier to learning is the operation of refund policies and guarantees. Both are often seen by students as exit strategies that may be exercised in lieu of completing a course. Thus, the possibility of a refund can and often does reduce student drive and their level of effort to successfully complete a course. OnLine Training's basic refund policy is thus - no refund.
However, there are exceptions. First, Online Training will fully honor the refund policy of our resellers - without question. Second, if a student enrolls in the wrong course, or an inappropriate course, and notifies Online Training within 24 hours of enrollment, a replacement course or refund will be made available.  If a refund is provided, a $25 administrative fee will be subtracted from the cost of the course. Third, students are encouraged to continue with their studies until they succeed.
Students are considered actively enrolled in a course until they complete the end of course examination, the post test, or the course registration expires. Course extensions are available upon approval. Course extensions must be requested before the expiration date is reached. An Extension Fee will be charged - all extensions are for only 1 month.  In all cases, after 3 extensions the course must be repurchased in order to continue.
Back to Top
_________________________________________
LINKED SITES
OnLine Training, Inc. may provide links and pointers to internet sites maintained by others ("third party sites"). OnLine Training, Inc. has not reviewed all of the third party sites linked to the Site and is not responsible for the contents of or any products or services offered in such third-party sites.
Back to Top
_________________________________________
BULLETIN BOARDS/CHAT ROOMS
and Non-Moderated List Servers
The Site may include bulletin boards, chat rooms and List Servers ("Bulletin Boards") which allow feedback to and real-time interaction between users.
1. OnLine Training, Inc. does not control the messages, information or files delivered to Bulletin Boards, unless otherwise noted therein, and has no obligation to monitor such Bulletin Boards. However, Online Training reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, that in OLT's sole discretion are objectionable or in violation of these Terms and Conditions.
2. It is a condition of your use of the Bulletin Boards and this Site that you do not:
a. Restrict or inhibit any other user from using and enjoying the Bulletin Boards;
b. post or transmit any unlawful, threatening, abusive, libelous, defamatory, obscene, vulgar, pornographic, profane or indecent information of any kind, including without limitation any transmission constituting or encouraging conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any local, state, national or foreign law;
c. post or transmit any information, software or other material which violates or infringes upon the rights of others, including material which is an invasion of privacy or publicity rights or which is protected by copyright, trademark or other proprietary right, or derivative works with respect thereto, without first obtaining permission from the owner or right holder;
d. post or transmit any information, software or other material which contains a virus or other harmful component; or
e. post, or transmit or in any way exploit any information, software or other material for commercial purposes or which contains advertising, promotion or marketing.
Back to Top
_________________________________________
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY/ DISCLAIMER
Your use and browsing of the Site is at your risk. If you are dissatisfied with any of the materials contained in the Site, or with any of these Terms and Conditions, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue accessing and using the Site.
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER OLT, NOR ANY OTHER PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING, OR DELIVERING THE SITE IS LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF YOUR ACCESS TO, OR USE OF, THE SITE. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, EVERYTHING ON THE SITE IS PROVIDED TO YOU "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT.
Back to Top
_________________________________________
JURISDICTIONAL ISSUES
The Site is controlled and operated by and from its offices within the State of Florida, United States of America. OnLine Training, Inc. makes no representation that Materials in the Site are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access this site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.
This agreement shall be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of Florida, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such State. Any action you, any third party or bring to enforce these Terms and Conditions or, in connection with, any matters related to this site shall be brought only in either the state or Federal Courts located in Palm Beach County, Florida, and you expressly consent to the jurisdiction of said courts. If any provision of this agreement shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the matters contained herein.
This Agreement will terminate immediately without notice from if in our sole discretion you fail to comply with any term or provision of this Agreement. Upon termination, you must destroy all materials obtained from this Site and all copies thereof, whether made under the terms of this Agreement or otherwise. In the event of termination, you are no longer authorized to access the Bulletin Boards and the restrictions imposed on you with respect to Materials downloaded from the Bulletin Boards and the disclaimers and limitations of liabilities set forth in this Agreement shall survive.
Back to Top
_________________________________________
OTHER
If any provision of this agreement shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.
OnLine Training, Inc. may at any time revise these Terms and Conditions by updating this posting. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then current Terms and Conditions to which you are bound.
Back to Top
